Guide to the Stanford University, Government and Community Relations, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1999-172
  - SU FY92 IDC Analysis #35 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Fraud in Research Rule-making 10/88 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - ABA Conference on Tax-Exempt Charitable Organizations: General Tax Binder 11/13-14/1986 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Conference Tax Binder: Appreciated Property P/B etc. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Senate Tax Binder General (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Ken Bloem/Molly Coye Meeting Briefing Book 12/12/92 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Senate Appropriations Subcommittee on Labor, Health & Human Services: David Korn Testimony 3/28/90 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Senate Tax Binder 1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - After the Tax Bill (U.S. Tax Reform Act of 1986) Binder (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - SU FY89-90 Report on IDC Waivers 5/7/1991 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - SU FY94-95 IDC Proposals (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Horton IDC Review III; 165-246 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Horton IDC Review IV; 247-323 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Horton IDC Review V; 324-387 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Horton IDC Review VI; 388-450 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Horton IDC Review VII; 451-514 4-5/1991 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - IDC Press Clippings: PA Weekly, etc.1992 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Selected Materials Relating to Indirect Costs Prepared for Members of the Advisory Panel on Standards on Accountability, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Loma Prieta Earthquake Damage at SU and Repairs Required by Applicable Codes; Background Material... for FEMA, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Horton IDC Review 1371-1407 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Horton IDC Review 1408-1440 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Horton IDC Review XXIV; 1441-1458 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Horton IDC Review XXV; 1459-1468 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - SU FY89-90 IDC Waiver Report 5/16/1991 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Tax Reform: Charitable Giving, Appreciated Property, Gifts, Non-Itemizers 1985 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Tax Reform: General, Government, Proposals & Positions (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Tax Reform: General, Status Updates, Press, Ad Hoc Tax Committee (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Tax Reform: Benefits-Pension, Educational Assistance, R&D Credit, Scholarships & Fellowships, State & Local Taxes (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Tax Reform: General, Briefs, Positions, Communications, Analyses, Lobby Letters (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Tax Reform: Bonds (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Tax Reform: Briefs, Communications, Proposals, Notes, Lobby Letters (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - SU/Hoover Testimony & Articles (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Reading Packet for Distribution (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Earthquake 89 1 & 2 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Harvard Research (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Research (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - MIT Research (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - SU Dingell Complete Briefing Book with Attachments, I (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Misc. reports & Correspondence re: MOUs, etc. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Loma Prieta Earthquake Damage at SU "incomplete, do not use" 5/1992 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Appeal to the Regional Director of FEMA Region IX (re: Geology Corner Damage) 1993 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - FEMA (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - IDC Anthologies/Indices (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Earthquake Special Session November 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Damaged buildings maps (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Horton IDC Review VIII 515-583 5-6/1991 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Horton IDC Review IX; 584-650 7/1991 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Horton IDC Review X; 651-708 8-9/1991 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Book 13 Memoranda of Understanding between SU and US Government (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - IDC Press Releases V (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - IDC Press Releases VI (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Audio-Visual Materials:
    - SU Alumni Association, Donald Kennedy Speech in Senate Caucus Room, 2/19/91 (VHS cassette) (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - 20/20 Lead-in and Story Only (VHS cassette) (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Bay Area Newsmakers - KQED Tape off Air (VHS cassette) (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - News Coverage of SU Hearings 3/13 - 3/14/91 (VHS cassette) (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Biddle on KGO, 1/7/92 (audio cassette) (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - KQED - Biddle 9/25/92 (audio cassette) (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - House Committee Hearings: GAO Testimony I, GAO Testimony II, GAO/DCAA Testimony, DCAA/ONR Testimony, ONR Testimony, SU Testimony (7 VHS cassettes) (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - C-SPAN - House Committee Hearings (9 VHS cassettes) (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2001-076
  - Dingell Committee Briefing Book – Table of Contents (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dingell Committee Briefing Book – Testimony (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dingell Committee Briefing Book – General (1) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dingell Committee Briefing Book – General (2) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dingell Committee Briefing Book – Unallowable Items (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dingell Committee Briefing Book – Specific Items (1) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dingell Committee Briefing Book – Specific Items (2) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Indirect cost – news clippings, Jan.-Mar. 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "Stanford University's Response to Challenges to the Memoranda of Understanding," March 4, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Peat, Marwick, Mitchell & Co. Study of Indirect Cost Rates of Organizations Performing Federally Sponsored Research, prepared for Stanford University, November 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - RESTRICTED FOLDERS:
    (FILED WITH "RESTRICTED FOLDERS FROM ASSORTED SC COLLECTIONS" IN GW 403)
    - UCSF/STANFORD – legislation, 1996-97 (Folder R1)
    - UCSF/STANFORD – correspondence and memos (1 of 3) (Folder R2)
    - UCSF/STANFORD – correspondence and memos (2 of 3) (Folder R3)
    - UCSF/STANFORD – correspondence and memos (3 of 3) (Folder R4)